<?xml version="1.0"?>
<question id="EM_35" module="EM">
  <questionText>Carrie wanted to find out which was harder, a penny or a nickel, so she did a scratch test. How would this tell her which is harder?</questionText>
  <referenceAnswers>
    <referenceAnswer id="EM_35-a1">The harder coin will scratch the other.</referenceAnswer>
  </referenceAnswers>
  <studentAnswers>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.384.1" accuracy="incorrect">You could tell if it has the hardest if most of it came off.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.387.1" accuracy="correct">If just the penny could scratch and the nickel could not the penny is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.391.1" accuracy="correct">Whichever one was damaged most was less hard.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.398.1" accuracy="incorrect">Rub them against a crystal.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.403.1" accuracy="correct">Which had less scratches.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.408.1" accuracy="incorrect">If it makes a scratch or a little dent.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.418.1" accuracy="incorrect">Well she can take the penny and the nickel and rub them together.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.436.1" accuracy="correct">The one that is scratched is softer.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.437.1" accuracy="incorrect">She could tell which is harder by getting a rock and seeing if the penny or nickel would scratch it. Whichever one does is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.441.1" accuracy="incorrect">Maybe he should scratch even other then when you are done see if one have scratches.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.444.1" accuracy="incorrect">It would tell her because she could scratch the penny on the nickel and the nickel on the penny and see which one is scratched.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.487.1" accuracy="correct">In order to tell which is harder, else would have to see if the penny and nickel leave a mark to see which is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.490.1" accuracy="correct">By the one that leave a mark on one. That means that that one is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.493.1" accuracy="incorrect">The one that got scratch each penny or a nickel got scratch.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.496.1" accuracy="incorrect">She can scratch it and see which one scratch the rock or mineral.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.497.1" accuracy="correct">If the penny gets scratched the nickel is harder and if the nickel gets scratched then the penny is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.500.1" accuracy="correct">The nickel is the hardest because is you scratch it with a penny it will not scratch but the nickel could because it is so much.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.501.1" accuracy="correct">You get a penny or a nickel if one of them scratches the metal it is hard.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.503.1" accuracy="correct">She would know because the one that is scratched is the one that is least hard and the one that is not scratched is the one that is hardest.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.507.1" accuracy="correct">How you would know that one of them is harder is for say if the nickel never a scratch the penny, and the penny got scratch by the nickel then the nickel would be harder than the penny that is how you would which one is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.510.1" accuracy="correct">The one that got a scratch is not hard.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.561.1" accuracy="incorrect">A paperclip is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.565.1" accuracy="correct">The one that is harder will scratch the less harder one.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.568.1" accuracy="incorrect">I do not know.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.569.1" accuracy="incorrect">Fire.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.570.1" accuracy="incorrect">The nickel because it is bigger and it harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.571.1" accuracy="incorrect">By using your hand.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.572.1" accuracy="correct">If it left a scratch.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.575.1" accuracy="incorrect">I do not know.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.598.1" accuracy="incorrect">The nickel is the heavier and the penny is the lighter.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.599.1" accuracy="correct">You can rub the penny and the nickel together. The one with the mark and a scratch is the least hardest the one with no mark or scratch is the hardest.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.603.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because of it he you scratch with a penny.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.609.1" accuracy="correct">Rub them together and whichever one has a scratch or a mark the is softer and the one that has nothing on it is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.616.1" accuracy="correct">Rub to penny with nickel and whichever one had a scratch is some.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.632.1" accuracy="correct">She would scratch the rocks together the one that scratches is softer.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.35.647.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nickel is harder.</studentAnswer>
  </studentAnswers>
</question>
