<?xml version="1.0"?>
<question id="ME_28b" module="ME">
  <questionText>Look at the picture on the right. Label the poles on each magnet. (The bottom 2 magnets are stuck together, the others are not.) What is the rule that explains why you labeled the poles the way you did?</questionText>
  <referenceAnswers>
    <referenceAnswer id="ME_28b-a1">Like poles repel and opposite poles attract.</referenceAnswer>
  </referenceAnswers>
  <studentAnswers>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-1.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because they are repelling each other always.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-10.1" accuracy="correct">The magnets are not touching because they cannot attract to each other if they are north to north or south to south.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-11.1" accuracy="incorrect">The magnets will maybe not stick because the force of the magnets will maybe the pencil is long and the magnets cannot feel the other magnets.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-12.1" accuracy="incorrect">They are repelling.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-13.1" accuracy="incorrect">The magnets are on the side when they repel each other.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-14.1" accuracy="incorrect">They are on the same side.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-15.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings do not touch each other because the magnets are facing positive to negative.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-16.1" accuracy="incorrect">They do not touch each other because one side of the magnet has a force and the other side stick to each other because they do not have a force.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-17.1" accuracy="correct">The magnets do not touch each other because either the north and north sides are facing each other or on the south and south sides are facing each other.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-18.1" accuracy="correct">The rings do not touch each other because the rings are magnets so they repel because 2 south and north facing each other.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-19.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because the rings are magnets and they are facing each other on the same side.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-2.1" accuracy="correct">The magnets do not touch because the same poles are together so they all repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-20.1" accuracy="incorrect">They do not touch each other because the force of magnetism is repelling them away from each other.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-21.1" accuracy="incorrect">The magnets do not touch because if you flip the magnet to the other side it will not stick because it makes them different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-23.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings are not touch each other because they are not facing the right way.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-24.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings are made out of metal because they are repelling.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-28.1" accuracy="incorrect">The magnets are not touching because the magnetic force is making the magnets repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-29.1" accuracy="incorrect">They are not touching each other because they are repelling.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-3.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because they are not attracting.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-30.1" accuracy="incorrect">The magnets are not touching because they are flipped around a certain way that they do not stick instead they repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-31.1" accuracy="correct">They are not touching each other because either the North and North part of the magnets are touching or the south and south are touching.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-32.1" accuracy="correct">They are not touching because there are a north and south on a magnet and the north is facing the other north.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-33.1" accuracy="incorrect">The north pole and another north pole are touching on the magnet or the south pole and south pole which makes them repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-34.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because the magnets have a north and south pole and if the north touches the north or visa-versa north the will not touch.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-35.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings do not touch each other because if the magnets are not the right way they will repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-36.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings do not touch because the magnets were facing the same way which makes them float.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-37.1" accuracy="correct">They do not touch each other because if you put magnet the magnets like this will not attract North to North. If you put magnets like this it will attract North to South. If you put it like this it will not attract South to South.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-4.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings do not attach each other because they are flipped upside down.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-5.1" accuracy="correct">The rings do not touch because the top is south pole is the one below it is the south pole. When the poles are north and south they attract.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-6.1" accuracy="incorrect">The rings do not touch because the rings are just magnets and the magnets are on the repel side.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-7.1" accuracy="incorrect">They are not touching each other because they repel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="ME.28b.xx-9.1" accuracy="incorrect">Each magnet is pushing away from the magnet so they are attracting.</studentAnswer>
  </studentAnswers>
</question>
